National Extension Association of Family and Consumer Sciences, New York Affiliate records, 1931-2005
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
- Series I. Awards
  - General Application Form: Program Excellence Through Research Award: Charlotte W. Coffman, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - General Application Form: News Article: Theresa C. Mayhew, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Carolyn O. Boegly Outstanding Leadership Award: Dr. Sue Miles, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Distinguished Service Awards, c.a. 1999 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Application: Jeanne M. Darling, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Awards Programs, 1998-2005 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Awards Programs, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Awards Programs, 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Awards Programs, 1984-1990 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Awards Programs, 1979-1983 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Awards and Recognition, 1982-1992 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Award Lists, 1946-2000 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Professional Improvement Special Service Award, 1980s (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Awards, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Awards, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Awards, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Awards, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Awards, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Awards, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Awards, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Awards, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
  - Awards, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
  - Awards, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
  - Awards, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Series II. Newsletters and Brochures
  - FSC newsletter, 1974-1977 (Box 4)
  - Newsletters, etc. (binder 2, part 2), 1967-1970 (Box 4)
  - NYSAEHE Newsletters, 1977-1996 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - NEAFCS Newsletters, 1997-2002 (Box 11, Folder 4A)
  - "Reporter", 1970-1975 (Box 4)
  - "Reporter", 1975-1977 (Box 4)
  - "Reporter", 1980-1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "Reporter", 1992-1997 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Newsletters, 1990-1993 (Box 7)
  - Brochures, 1970s (Box 11, Folder 1)